Your Highness! Alec!
Prince ! Prince Alek !
Are you alright?!
Est-ce que ça va !?
Something's wrong!
C'est pas normal…
The wounds are turning purple?
Ça tourne au violet !
Don't tell me… he was poisoned?!
Il y avait du poison ?!
What should I do…?
Que faire… ?
If it were Lily, she'd use her powers to heal him…
Si Lili était là, elle pourrait utiliser son pouvoir pour le soigner…
And the real Loneal might have been able to use a potion…
Le vrai Lonile aurait pu utiliser une potion…
But I can't do anything…
Mais moi… Je ne sais rien faire…
Alec…!
Alek… !
As long as you don't give up, you will find a way.
Si tu persévères, tu trouveras la voie.
That's right, I need to think…
Il a raison…
If I don't give up… I just have to think…
Je ne dois pas abandonner…
I…
Je…
I want to save him!
Je veux le sauver… !
What's going on?
Qu'est-ce qu'il se passe ?
There's some kind of light…?
Cette lumière…
His wounds… are disappearing…?
Ses blessures sont en train de disparaître ?
It's so warm…  What's this light…?
C'est chaud… Chette lumière… ?
Alec!
Alek !
Thank… goodness…!
Dieu merci…
Loneal!
Lonile !
Where am I?
Où suis-je ?
I see you're awake.
Tu es réveillé ?
This is my second home.
C'est ma maison de vacances.
Are you alright?! What about your wounds?!
Tu vas bien ? Tes blessures…
See for yourself.
Alors ?
His arm… It's all healed!
Elles sont parties !
They really healed…
Tu es soigné…
It's all thanks to your magic.
C'est grâce à ta magie.
Thank you.
Merci.
Enough about me. Were you hurt?
Mais  toi, tu as des blessures ?
Protecting you is my responsibility.
C'est mon devoir de te protéger.
How about I check you over too?
Laisse-moi regarder ton corps pour vérifier si tout va bien.
Check me…?
Mon corps ?
Y-Your highness…
P-Prince…
Does it hurt anywhere?
Est-que tu as mal quelque part ?
No… I-I'm fine…
N-Non… J-Je vais bien…
He's just checking to see if I'm okay…
Je sais qu'il vérifie juste si je vais bien…
But his touch makes me so happy…
Mais son toucher me rend heureux…
You seem fine.
Tu as l'air d'aller.
I don't see anything
Je ne vois pas de blessures.
Oh my… What do we have here?
Oh oh…
Loneal…
Lonile…
S-Sorry…
Désolé…
I tried to hold back…
Je voulais me retenir, mais…
But I don't think I can keep it up much longer.
Je doute de pourvoir résister plus longtemps.
I want to feel all of you…
Je te veux.
A-Alec…
P-Prince…
I can't… hold back either…
Ça me fait drôle…
Then… I hope this will make you feel even better.
Tu es devenu bien sensible ici.
It's my fault that you're in such a state.
C'est ma faute.
So, I need to take responsibility and make you enjoy every last minute of it.
Je dois en prendre la responsabilité et bien m'occuper de toi.
It's already too much…
C'est déjà trop…
D-Don't stretch it… any more…
Pas la peine d'élargir mon trou…
If I don't loosen you up, then it'll hurt when you take me in.
Il vaut mieux l'élargir maintenant, sinon ça va te faire mal quand je vais rentrer en toi.
Alec can't be with a side-character like me…
Alek ne devrait pas être avec un personnage secondaire comme moi…
But I can't be without him anymore.
Mais je ne peux plus me passer de lui…
I was so afraid when I thought he might die…
J'avais si peur quand j'ai cru qu'il allait mourir…
Loneal.
Lonile.
Let me see your face.
Je veux voir ton visage.
But he's alive… And…
Mais il est en vie… Avec moi…
Alec…! Alec…!
Alek…! Alek…!
I want to feel his touch even more!
Je le veux encore plus…
Loneal… Let's cum together.
Lonile, jouissons ensemble.
What do you mean?
Comment ça?
W-Well…
E-Eh bien…
I know for a fact that he was injured… As well as poisoned, but…
Je suis sûr qu'il a été empoisonné, mais…
This morning,
Ce matin,
the prince returned to school with Loneal, and appeared to be uninjured.
le prince était à l'école avec Lonile… Sans la moindre blessure.
His wound disappeared?
Sa blessure a disparu ?
That would be possible with the Holy Bride's power…
Ce serait possible avec le pourvoir de la sainte…
But who could've done it?
Mais qui… ?
Seems like I found something much more interesting than that notebook.
Il semblerait que j'aie trouvé quelque chose de bien plus intéressant qu'un livret.
My dearest Loneal.
Mon cher Lonile.